## **ALLISON NAULT**

allisonrnault@gmail.com | C: 616-204-2600 | 1835 W Erie St, Apt 1, Chicago, IL 60622

# Summary

A highly motivated team leader with 2 years of professional sales experience in the fitness industry. A top performer able to leverage Hubspot CRM tools to increase productivity, ensure quality standards, and implement best practices. Experienced in overseeing multiple departments, training staff, and developing team members.

## Skills

- Customer service and sales
- Managing multiple departments
- 2 years CRM experience
- Payroll processing
- Certified AMGA Climbing Wall Instructor
- Employee training and development
- Leading team meetings
- Sales and outreach management
- Client account management
- Scheduling

# **Experience**

02/2020 - Current Brooklyn Boulders Chicago, IL

## **Regional Operations Manager**

**Full Time** 

April 2022 - Current

- Supported product growth by ensuring programs, classes and other offerings were properly staffed and scheduled
- Oversaw group fitness & personal training, climbing programs, youth programs, retail, customer experience, and front desk operations for two Chicago Facilities.
- Prepared and submitted bi-weekly payroll for two facilities (~84 employees).
- Facilitated monthly staff scheduling at two facilities to ensure maximum efficiency and productivity of all team members.
- Directly managed and supported the Customer Experience
  Team responsible for responding to online service requests.

**Lead Community Advisor** 

### **Full Time**

January 2021 - April 2022

- Built a collaborative sales team culture with a focus on training, coaching, and implementing best practices to unleash potential of sales representatives to maximize results.
- Created workflows and automations within Hubspot CRM to improve guest traffic management and membership sales
- Increased national membership base ~3x to 10k active members between April 1 - September 2021, achieving best sales months ever in company history in Q2 of 2021.

### **Community Advisor**

**Full Time** 

August 2020 - January 2021

- Leader in membership sales, averaging 30+ sales/ month
- Proficient in using Hubspot CRM for sales outreach and lead management

#### **Front Desk Operations**

**Full Time** 

February 2020 - August 2020

- Implemented stringent COVID-19 safety protocols, delivering 40,000+ unique guest check ins in 2H 2020 without any reported virus transmission within facilities.
- Provided customer service to guests and members, including check-ins, facility orientations, retail POS, and COVID screenings
- Opening and closing procedures
- Helped with Facility cleanliness
- Climbing instruction and personal coaching

07/2012 - 02/2020 Retail Store Manager Beadniks Chicago Chicago, IL

Full Time

- Managed store appearance, including merchandising and displays, signage, decorations and cleaning.
- Delivered excellent customer service by greeting and assisting

each customer.

- Shared product knowledge with customers while making personal recommendations.
- Updated and edited store website.
- Interviewed, supervised and trained employees.
- Oversaw inventory management.
- Stocked and restocked inventory when shipments were received.
- Instructed workshops on jewelry making techniques.
- Constructed custom jewelry designs for customers and the store.
- Worked closely with jewelry designers to fabricate their designs.
- Oversaw daily cash register operations.
- Went on buying trips to bead and gemstone conventions.

08/2011 - 05/2012 **Co- Instructor** 

After School

Matters

Chicago, IL

Part Time

- Worked with high school students to create a multi-media, mosaic mural for George Washington High School.
- Taught basic design, mosaic, painting and sculpture techniques.
- Oversaw fabrication and installation of the mural.

06/2011 - 08/2011

**Assistant Instructor** 

Chicago Public Art Part Time

Group

Chicago, IL

- Worked in partnership with After School Matters to create Aqua Interlude and Reflection, a 1,500-square-foot mosaic for the city of Chicago located in the Columbus Drive underpass to the Museum Campus.
- Aided lead artists in teaching students how to cut and set mosaic tiles.
- Assisted in the installation of the mosaic.

# **Education and Training**

2011 Bachelor of Fine Arts in Sculpture and Printmaking

Elmhurst, IL Elmhurst College